<resources>
    <string name="app_name">weatherApp</string>
    <string name="find_climate">Find the climate of fav place?</string>
    <string name="want_video">Want to see some video?</string>
    <string name="thunderstorm">A thunderstorm is a meteorological event characterized by the occurrence of lightning, thunder, heavy rain, and sometimes hail. It typically arises from the rapid upward movement of warm, moist air that can result in the formation of towering cumulonimbus clouds. Within these clouds, the temperature and moisture differences lead to the development of electrical charges, resulting in the spectacular discharge of lightning. The accompanying thunder is caused by the explosive expansion of air as it heats and cools rapidly due to the lightning. Thunderstorms can be accompanied by strong winds and can pose a range of hazards, including flash flooding, strong gusts, and occasionally, tornadoes. These powerful weather events are a common occurrence in many parts of the world </string>
    <string name="rainfall">Rainfall weather, also known as rainy weather, is characterized by the presence of precipitation in the form of rain. It is a common meteorological phenomenon that occurs when water droplets condense in the atmosphere and fall to the Earths surface. Rainfall can vary in intensity, from light drizzles to heavy downpours, and it plays a crucial role in maintaining the Earths ecosystem.</string>
    <string name="drizzle">Drizzle is a light and fine precipitation that consists of tiny water droplets falling from the sky. It typically occurs in the form of very fine raindrops, smaller in size than regular rain, and is often characterized by its gentle and mist-like quality. Drizzle is commonly associated with overcast or foggy weather conditions and can create a damp and misty atmosphere</string>
    <string name="snow">Snowy weather is characterized by the atmospheric phenomenon in which frozen water vapor falls from the sky in the form of snowflakes. This meteorological occurrence occurs when the temperature in the atmosphere is low enough for water vapor to freeze into ice crystals. Snowfall can range from light flurries to heavy, accumulating snow, covering landscapes in a serene white blanket.</string>
    <string name="mist">Mist is a weather condition characterized by the presence of tiny water droplets suspended in the air, reducing visibility and creating a hazy or foggy atmosphere. It often occurs in the early morning or late evening when the ground cools, causing moisture in the air to condense</string>
    <string name="haze">Haze is a meteorological phenomenon characterized by a fine suspension of dust, smoke, or other dry particles in the air, which reduces visibility and imparts a milky or brownish tint to the atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="fog">Fog is a meteorological phenomenon characterized by the presence of thick, low-lying cloud formations near the Earths surface. It is primarily composed of tiny water droplets or ice crystals suspended in the air.</string>
    <string name="dusty">Dusty weather, often characterized by the presence of suspended particles and reduced visibility, can occur in various environmental settings. This type of weather condition typically arises in arid regions, deserts, or during specific atmospheric events like dust storms</string>
    <string name="sandy">Sandy weather typically refers to conditions in which fine particles of sand are suspended in the air, creating reduced visibility and potentially hazardous environments.</string>
    <string name="ash">Ash weather typically occurs in the aftermath of volcanic eruptions or wildfires when fine ash particles are suspended in the atmosphere and carried by winds</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear weather typically refers to a meteorological condition characterized by an absence of significant cloud cover or precipitation in the atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="squal">A squall is a sudden and intense burst of wind characterized by strong, gusty winds that can rapidly develop and last for a relatively short period of time, typically lasting less than 20 minutes</string>
    <string name="cloudy">Cloudy weather is a meteorological condition characterized by the presence of a significant amount of cloud cover in the sky. It is often associated with overcast or gray skies, resulting in reduced sunlight and subdued lighting</string>
<string name="smoke">Smoke weather conditions occur when the atmosphere is filled with fine particles and pollutants, resulting in reduced visibility and poor air quality</string>
</resources>